<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Lastest Thinking &#8211; Rikkeisoft &#8211; Your trusted IT provider</title>
	<atom:link href="https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://rikkeisoft.com</link>
	<description>Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 03:34:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.7</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The millionaire guide on pizza to help you get rich</title>
		<link>https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/256/the-millionaire-guide-on-pizza-to-help-you-get-rich/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chitv@rikkeisoft.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 05:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Lastest Thinking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rikkeisoft.com/?p=256</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I like the look of this car. It is very comfortable. It get good gas mileage. I am very happy with my vehicle. I like the fact that it has performance as well as style. The interior looks like cars in a much higher class such as Mercedes Lexus etc. The engine has never given [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/256/the-millionaire-guide-on-pizza-to-help-you-get-rich/">The millionaire guide on pizza to help you get rich</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h3>I like the look of this car. It is very comfortable. It get good gas mileage.</h3>



<p id="block-177b0e90-2ab3-4b30-96e5-bff5f3134b37">I am very happy with my vehicle. I like the fact that it has performance as well as style. The interior looks like cars in a much higher class such as Mercedes Lexus etc. The engine has never given any problems. The car looks like the day it was purchased. I would definitely purchase another vehicle like mine. The sunroof is perfect for the warm summer days and the heated seats warm up so quickly on winter days.</p>



<p id="block-79d79dc3-48f9-407d-a86e-6af003dae9eb">Gets great gas mileage in town and on the road. Seat adjust great. Driver seat has 2 selection. Love the warm seats or the cold seat. It has leather seats that clean up great. Warranty was the reason I bought this car 100 thousand mile or 10 years is a great warranty.</p>



<h3 id="block-f1d199b1-f974-4df0-b937-a2a522e1f867">When international students went hungry, Canberra&#8217;s Indian community dug deep</h3>



<p id="block-9ea067b4-34c1-4e45-a04d-292a02c2cae5">The car looks like the day it was purchased. I would definitely purchase another vehicle like mine. Hyundai azera sedan gains more safety features, such as blind spot detection and lane change assist.8-inch LCD navigation multimedia interface is standard and includes google poi search and apple’s eyes-free siri integration. Plenty of standard features. Smooth ride quality. Quiet and spacious cabin. Large trunk. Long warranty coverage. I love my Hyundai azera limited. It has blind spot detection which has saved me many of times. It also has a backup camera so I can back up into parking spots easily.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/img2.png" alt="" class="wp-image-37" width="775" height="567" srcset="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/img2.png 370w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/img2-300x219.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 775px) 100vw, 775px" /><figcaption>Dinner and a Rematch by <strong>Jim Pollock</strong></figcaption></figure>



<h4 id="block-82561a27-6733-4040-8948-fe94938e8262">Oat cake pastry powder fruitcake I love. Dessert topping donut caramels jelly beans tiramisu. Croissant pie gingerbread dessert I love danish apple pie chocolate.</h4>



<p id="block-dc24d3c5-316d-4ca8-9178-bc71a841de5c">I am very happy with my vehicle. I like the fact that it has performance as well as style. The interior looks like cars in a much higher class such as Mercedes Lexus etc. The engine has never given any problems. The car looks like the day it was purchased. I would definitely purchase another vehicle like mine. The sunroof is perfect for the warm summer days and the heated seats warm up so quickly on winter days.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/256/the-millionaire-guide-on-pizza-to-help-you-get-rich/">The millionaire guide on pizza to help you get rich</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How are Blockchain changing  Vietnam industries?</title>
		<link>https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/502/how-are-blockchain-changing-vietnam-industries/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chitv@rikkeisoft.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Lastest Thinking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rikkeisoft.com/2021/11/17/how-are-blockchain-changing-vietnam-industries/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#160; Why is blockchain capable of change? Due to its efficiency (increasing transaction speed), authentication (right to confirm transactions) and transparency (information in block is only available to users), blockchain technology is considered to be radically changing the operation of many industries today. It was first introduced to the world in 2008 and has tended [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/502/how-are-blockchain-changing-vietnam-industries/">How are Blockchain changing  Vietnam industries?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><meta charset="utf-8"></p>
<p dir="ltr">Why is blockchain capable of change?</p>
<p>Due to its efficiency (increasing transaction speed), authentication (right to confirm transactions) and transparency (information in block is only available to users), blockchain technology is considered to be radically changing the operation of many industries today. It was first introduced to the world in 2008 and has tended to develop in Vietnam since 2018. In the system&#8217;s transaction procedure, all data is encrypted into blocks and concatenated into a secure chain.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="900" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/211117%20-%20BLOCKCHAIN-01.png" width="1600"></p>
<p>So In what areas specifically does blockchain lead the way it operates?</p>
<p><em><b id="docs-internal-guid-d3df0eb0-7fff-ab54-eb32-c4b1cc3fb3a6">&nbsp;</b>Logistic</em></p>
<p>In Vietnam, blockchain technology has significantly impacted and changed the operation method of a number of fields. Thanks to blockchain&#8217;s transparency,&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">customers can trace and verify the origin of products during the supply and delivery of goods. Previously, this information was frequently stored in traditional ledgers, which contained inconsistent and discontinuous data. Blockchain enables all information to reach customers efficiently, from the manufacturing to finished product process.&nbsp;</p>
<p>2,&nbsp;Real Estate Market</p>
<p><b>I</b>n the real estate sector, large value transactions often take time, cost and documentation to complete, which has a negative impact on market liquidity and transparency. From that view, blockchain handles this problem by digitizing with its own code, reducing time and expenses while enhancing transaction security.</p>
<p>3,&nbsp;Fintech</p>
<p>Moreover, financial and banking transactions have made a remarkable change as a result of this technology. One of the applications of blockchain in this field is the function of identifying customers based on distributed ledger. Hence, they can conduct online transactions (such as lending credit or capital funding requests) while maintaining high levels of information security, instead of face-to-face transactions.&nbsp;</p>
<p><b>4,&nbsp;</b>Healthcare services</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the application of this technology, healthcare services have had a positive change when it can provide an effective solution in the management of the pharmaceutical supply chain and be able to trace the origin of the drug to avoid counterfeiting.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The advantages of blockchain&#8217;s data security and transparency enable both doctors and patients to access health information in electronic health records which depend on the level of content access right. Compared with manual updating, blockchain technology can prevent the risk of patient data leakage because of unchangeable information.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Trends:&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">If the goal of the 4.0 technology era in Vietnam is to use cut-edging technology to best serve human needs, blockchain will be the key to set a foundation that contributes to positive impact in many fields. In the future, blockchain is expected to continue to gain traction in areas such as education (storing/looking/ looking up the origins of diplomas) and tourism (booking hotels, air tickets), as well as in the gaming industry with new play models.</p>
<p><b id="docs-internal-guid-d3df0eb0-7fff-ab54-eb32-c4b1cc3fb3a6">I</b>f you’re intrigued by reading this article and want to apply Blockchain Technology for your business, let’s visit us on the website <a href="https://rikkeisoft.com/en#">https://rikkeisoft.com/en#</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">To read more technology blogs, dig into https://rikkeisoft.com/en/blog#.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/502/how-are-blockchain-changing-vietnam-industries/">How are Blockchain changing  Vietnam industries?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top 3 Blockchain applications in business activities</title>
		<link>https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/579/top-3-blockchain-applications-in-business-activities-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chitv@rikkeisoft.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 03:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Lastest Thinking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rikkeisoft.com/2021/11/08/top-3-blockchain-applications-in-business-activities-2/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The blockchain is now an exciting new alternative to traditional currency, centralized banking, and transaction methods that are changing the way we handle financial transactions and alternative uses that will change the world. In short, blockchain is a distributed ledger that maintains a continuously-growing list of every transaction across every network distributed over tens of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/579/top-3-blockchain-applications-in-business-activities-2/">Top 3 Blockchain applications in business activities</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-d497de4d-7fff-e2cb-9f0f-bca3c6506f57">T</b><strong>he blockchain is now an exciting new alternative to traditional currency, centralized banking, and transaction methods that are changing the way we handle financial transactions and alternative uses that will change the world. In short, blockchain is a distributed ledger that maintains a continuously-growing list of every transaction across every network distributed over tens of thousands of computers. This makes it almost impossible to hack, changing the way banking is done.</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-d497de4d-7fff-e2cb-9f0f-bca3c6506f57">In this blog, let Rikkeisoft talk about some of the best Blockchain applications and blockchain advantages which were earlier known as Crypto Currencies and Bitcoin.&nbsp;</b></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-d497de4d-7fff-e2cb-9f0f-bca3c6506f57">&nbsp;</b></p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="608" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/Untitled-1%20%5BRecovered%5D-01.png" width="1600"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">The term &#8220;smart contract&#8221; was originally developed in 1993, although it has only recently gained popularity as a result of the Ethereum Project&#8217;s introduction in 2013. &#8220;The Project is a decentralized platform that executes smart contracts: apps that run exactly as programmed without the risk of delay, censorship, fraud, or third-party interference,&#8221; according to the website.</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">According to Chris DeRose of American Banker, smart contracts are &#8220;self-automated computer programs that can carry out the conditions of any contract.&#8221; &#8220;It is a financial security kept in escrow by a network and routed to beneficiaries based on future events and computer code,&#8221; according to the definition. As a result, businesses will be able to use ‘smart contracts’ to bypass regulations and “lower the costs for a subset of our most common financial transactions.”&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Smart contracts are now appropriate to be used in a wide range of areas. From commercial activities to specialized sectors such as health, election monitoring, logistics chain involvement, etc., it includes a lot of benefits, including automation, accuracy, high security, and cost savings.</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="608" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/Untitled-1%20%5BRecovered%5D-02.png" width="1600"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">In the real world, money transfer has gained utmost popularity with its unique feature of cross-border payments, exchange for cryptocurrencies, real-time ledger system, and all of this by lowering the third-party fees. We can see a lot of such blockchain use cases.</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">TPBank is the first Vietnamese bank to use blockchain for international money transfers successfully. Customers of TPBank will no longer have to wait several hours to make a money transfer from Japan to a TPBank account because these transactions will now take only a few minutes, thanks to RippleNet, which applies blockchain technology to international money transfers. RippleNet is a support platform that uses Distributed Ledger Technology (DLT) based on the contemporary Blockchain and API platform to assist transactions to be completed faster. By joining RippleNet, all parties are kept up to date on the status and information of each transaction.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">&nbsp;</h2>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="608" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/Untitled-1%20%5BRecovered%5D-03.png" width="1600"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Since the blockchain&#8217;s origins in cryptocurrencies, it&#8217;s only reasonable to apply it to employee compensation. &#8220;If your company regularly sends salary to international workers, then introducing Bitcoin into the payroll process might be a huge cost saver,&#8221; says Geoff Weiss on Entrepreneur.</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Bitwage, which claims to be the world’s first Bitcoin-based payroll service, will “circumvent the costly fees associated with transferring money internationally, as well as the time it takes for such funds to move from bank to bank, payments made via Bitcoin can save both money and time for employers and employees alike.” Bitwage’s founder and COO, Jonathan Chester says that by using a public ledger of all transactions in chronological order “you can actually see exactly where the money is throughout the process.”</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Then there is paying remote employees and contractors. Again, this form of payment is a very large part of my personal business and something many big companies (and banks) are betting on this year.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">&nbsp;</h2>
<p style="text-align:center"><img alt="" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/Untitled-1%20%5BRecovered%5D-04.png"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">There are many advantages to using blockchain. Here are the most significant ones&nbsp;</p>
<ol>
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<h3 dir="ltr" role="presentation" style="text-align: justify;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-d497de4d-7fff-e2cb-9f0f-bca3c6506f57">Security</b></h3>
</li>
</ol>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">With so many security provisions in place, blockchain is among the most secure technologies available to us. As a result, tampering with it is nearly impossible.&nbsp;</p>
<ol start="2">
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<h3 dir="ltr" role="presentation" style="text-align: justify;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-d497de4d-7fff-e2cb-9f0f-bca3c6506f57">Flexibility</b></h3>
</li>
</ol>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">From healthcare to transport, you can use blockchain in any industry. All you need is a working knowledge of blockchain and the industry you want to implement it in.&nbsp;</p>
<ol start="3">
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<h3 dir="ltr" role="presentation" style="text-align: justify;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-d497de4d-7fff-e2cb-9f0f-bca3c6506f57">Automation</b></h3>
</li>
</ol>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Most of the operations in a blockchain are done by software implementations. Such automation makes blockchain networks highly efficient.&nbsp;</p>
<ol start="4">
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<h3 dir="ltr" role="presentation" style="text-align: justify;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-d497de4d-7fff-e2cb-9f0f-bca3c6506f57">Transparency</b></h3>
</li>
</ol>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Every change made in the blockchain is visible to all the users that have access to the same. This keeps things transparent and enhances the versatility of this technology.&nbsp;</p>
<ol start="5">
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<h3 dir="ltr" role="presentation" style="text-align: justify;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-d497de4d-7fff-e2cb-9f0f-bca3c6506f57">Global Adaptation</b></h3>
</li>
</ol>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Organizations all across the globe are implementing or trying to implement blockchain in one way or another. It is a globally recognized and adopted technology, and it’s gaining popularity.&nbsp;</p>
<ol start="6">
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<h3 dir="ltr" role="presentation" style="text-align: justify;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-d497de4d-7fff-e2cb-9f0f-bca3c6506f57">Reliability</b></h3>
</li>
</ol>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Every interested party in a blockchain transaction is certified and verified. This removes the need for double records and makes the transaction process much more reliable.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-d497de4d-7fff-e2cb-9f0f-bca3c6506f57">Conclusion</b></h2>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Blockchain is certainly one of the most versatile and useful technologies currently available, and now is the best time to enter this sector.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">If you’re intrigued by reading this article and want to apply Blockchain Technology for your business, let’s visit us on the website https://rikkeisoft.com/en#.</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">To read more technology blogs, dig into https://rikkeisoft.com/en/blog#.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/579/top-3-blockchain-applications-in-business-activities-2/">Top 3 Blockchain applications in business activities</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>IoT trends around the world: Smart Factory of the post-pandemic future</title>
		<link>https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/498/iot-trends-around-the-world-smart-factory-of-the-post-pandemic-future/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chitv@rikkeisoft.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 01:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Lastest Thinking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rikkeisoft.com/2021/10/27/iot-trends-around-the-world-smart-factory-of-the-post-pandemic-future/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#160; The Smart Factory model, which includes typical Industrial Revolution 4.0 applications (IoT, AI, big data, cloud computing, etc. ), is an excellent way to improve production and business management. It is obvious that the Smart Factory is a significant movement advance and a breakthrough in comparison to the previous three revolutions. People will be [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/498/iot-trends-around-the-world-smart-factory-of-the-post-pandemic-future/">IoT trends around the world: Smart Factory of the post-pandemic future</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><meta charset="utf-8"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-67bb36ba-7fff-0b73-8bc7-8cc0750a0246">The Smart Factory model, which includes typical Industrial Revolution 4.0 applications (IoT, AI, big data, cloud computing, etc. ), is an excellent way to improve production and business management. It is obvious that the Smart Factory is a significant movement advance and a breakthrough in comparison to the previous three revolutions. People will be able to control and operate all production activities and digitize all activities with the help of this solution.</b></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-67bb36ba-7fff-0b73-8bc7-8cc0750a0246">In this post, Rikkeisoft will explain the smart factory model and the incredible benefits it provides to humans.</b></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="409" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/SMART%20FACTORY-02.png" width="1600"></p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">According to Deloitte Insights, the Smart Factory solution, also known as factory 4.0, is a significant step forward when a traditional automated production system is connected and processed with continuous production and business data, allowing the system to learn and adapt to changing market needs. As a result, operations will be more efficient, flexible, and able to forecast and self-regulate while also reducing downtime.</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">The real power of a Smart Factory lies in its ability to evolve and change throughout the organizational change process, whether it is influenced by market demand, expanding into new markets, developing new products and services, forecasting and meeting the needs of the operation, maintenance, incorporating new technologies and processes, or changes in the production process in near real-time. The connection is the most significant feature of a smart factory. Basic manufacturing processes and materials must be connected in order to create the data needed to make timely decisions in smart factories.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="572" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/SMART%20FACTORY-04.png" width="1600"></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation"><b id="docs-internal-guid-67bb36ba-7fff-0b73-8bc7-8cc0750a0246">The proactive</b></p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Factory 4.0 solution is a proactive system that can respond to the market&#8217;s demanding and continuously changing demands. People may manage machinery, production equipment, monitor and digitize activities to establish an efficient system, reduce machine downtime, and increase the capacity to forecast and self-calibrate thanks to intelligent production systems. In addition, engineers may rely on the system&#8217;s analyses and forecasts to develop a switch strategy, quickly respond when issues arise, and ensure the safety of production activities.</p>
<ul>
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation"><b id="docs-internal-guid-67bb36ba-7fff-0b73-8bc7-8cc0750a0246">Flexible&nbsp;</b></p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Throughout its use, Smart Factory can adapt, upgrade, and grow quickly. Smart production systems enable businesses to actively improve their production processes in response to market demands, even expanding into new markets. As previously said, Smart Factory also has the capacity to forecast in order to assist organizations in making timely and suitable changes to new technologies and processes.</p>
<ul>
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation"><b id="docs-internal-guid-67bb36ba-7fff-0b73-8bc7-8cc0750a0246">Connected&nbsp;</b></p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Intelligently connecting all machines, assets, and human resources is a critical component of factory 4.0&#8217;s excellence. This improves operational efficiency and productivity by optimizing the data processing process. In addition, humans can make better use of their time and communicate with machines by utilizing wireless device connectivity.</p>
<ul>
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation"><b id="docs-internal-guid-67bb36ba-7fff-0b73-8bc7-8cc0750a0246">Optimized</b></p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">A Smart Factory not only provides superior, synchronous, and reliable features to the manufacturer, but it also improves efficiency by increasing productivity and asset operations efficiency. Therefore, increasing flexibility and optimal operations, automating many operations, creating a safer working environment, improving quality, and quickly preventing risks, and saving and optimizing costs.</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="516" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/SMART%20FACTORY-06(1).png" width="1600"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-67bb36ba-7fff-0b73-8bc7-8cc0750a0246">So, why are smart factories the future of the industry? Our Rikkeisoft IoT experts illustrate three key initiatives for big business to transform their sites into smart factories.&nbsp;</b></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">First, The Smart Factory enables companies to achieve their carbon neutrality goals. Customers, and society as a whole, now expect big businesses to set goals that align with climate science. It’s something that cannot be ignored and could even be detrimental to the business if companies don’t consider their carbon footprint. For example, many of our customers have already made carbon-neutral commitments, and it’s important for them to work with a partner with similar values and goals. It’s also clear that the opportunities are there. The global economic benefit of a low-carbon future is estimated to be USD26 trillion by 2030.</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Second, connectivity is a key enabler for a low-carbon future and a low-carbon economy. We’ve already seen the benefits of digitalization this year—fewer commutes to the office and more flexible work. In fact, digital technology can cut business flights by 50 percent. It has a huge impact. On a bigger scale, capabilities like IoT and machine learning means we can optimize existing physical infrastructure, and therefore reduce the need for more or bigger infrastructure in the future.</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Finally, sites like a 5G smart factory can be part of a wider effort to close the digital divide and take an active role in creating future jobs. Today, there’s a significant shortage of STEM professionals (Science, Technology, Engineering, and Mathematics) and a lack of people with the right skills to fill the jobs that’ll be needed as part of the digital transformation of industries.</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="409" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/SMART%20FACTORY-07.png" width="1600"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">In conclusion, the smart factory benefits manufacturers by creating a safer, efficient, and more reliable operation. Companies will need to adopt digital technologies in order to meet consumers&#8217; rising expectations of faster delivery times, free shipping, options to customize products, more transparency, and lower costs. Furthermore, the demands on the manufacturing industry will continue due to the trend for more on-demand production and the ever-present drive to reduce costs. The smart factory is a direct way for manufacturers to excel in a competitive and dynamic marketplace as they&#8217;ll use digital innovation to improve supply chain efficiencies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/498/iot-trends-around-the-world-smart-factory-of-the-post-pandemic-future/">IoT trends around the world: Smart Factory of the post-pandemic future</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>IoT solution for the new 4.0 Agriculture</title>
		<link>https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/577/iot-solution-for-the-new-4-0-agriculture-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chitv@rikkeisoft.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 03:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Lastest Thinking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rikkeisoft.com/2021/10/20/iot-solution-for-the-new-4-0-agriculture-2/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Information Technology 4.0 era has had a significant impact on all aspects of life, including agriculture. The agriculture sector has traditionally been associated with conventional characteristics, but the agricultural industry is not immune to the impact of the Information Technology 4.0 wave. IoT technology with factories, farms, and a smart agricultural ecosystem is one [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/577/iot-solution-for-the-new-4-0-agriculture-2/">IoT solution for the new 4.0 Agriculture</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">The Information Technology 4.0 era has had a significant impact on all aspects of life, including agriculture. The agriculture sector has traditionally been associated with conventional characteristics, but the agricultural industry is not immune to the impact of the Information Technology 4.0 wave. IoT technology with factories, farms, and a smart agricultural ecosystem is one of the new technologies contributing to beneficial improvements in the agriculture business. Let’s look at IoT’s great solutions and benefits to this industry in this Rikkeisoft blog!</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="409" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/211019%20-%20smartfarm-02.png" width="1600"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">The ease of internet connectivity and cheap computing have made it possible to incorporate IoT solutions in farming. Here are some examples of how IoT can be used for the agriculture industry.&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation" style="text-align: justify;">Precision Farming: Also known as precision agriculture, precision farming can be thought of as anything that makes farming practice more controlled and accurate when raising livestock and growing crops. This is one of the most famous applications of IoT in the agricultural sector, and numerous organizations are leveraging this technique around the world.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation" style="text-align: justify;">Monitoring of climate conditions: A climate change monitoring system integrates satellite observations, ground-based data, and forecast models to monitor and forecast changes in the weather and climate. Probably the most popular smart agriculture gadgets are weather stations, combining various smart farming sensors. Located across the field, they collect various data from the environment and send it to the cloud. The provided measurements can be used to map the climate conditions, choose the appropriate crops, and take the required measures to improve their capacity (i.e., precision farming).</p>
</li>
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation" style="text-align: justify;">Smart Greenhouse automation: Greenhouse farming is a method of increasing agricultural, vegetable, and fruit yields. Greenhouses control environmental factors in one of two ways: manually or via a proportional control mechanism. Through IoT embedded systems, a smart greenhouse not only monitors but also manages the environment. As a result, there is no need for human intervention.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify;">From 2019-2020, Rikkeisoft has developed the “Smart Agriculture” solution for our Japanese customers. Rikkeisoft has successfully constructed an IoT-applied smart technology system to meet client needs effectively by understanding customer requirements for developing an automated monitoring and control system for a greenhouse vegetable garden. Rikkeisoft is more confident in applying the extraordinary advances of IoT to its products after the first IoT achievements in the agriculture industry. In the future, our team will continue to research and improve products for use in the country&#8217;s agricultural business, thereby boosting the harvest quality for Vietnamese farmers.</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="617" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/211019%20-%20smartfarm-02-04.png" width="1600"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-180ff46f-7fff-3389-c50c-dcacdc847069">&nbsp;</b>The use of IoT in agriculture has the potential to transform humans and the world as a whole. We are currently witnessing how harsh weather, eroding soil, dry areas, and collapsing ecosystems are making food production increasingly difficult and costly. Here are several benefits that IoT brings to the development of agriculture.&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation" style="text-align: justify;">Data collection: All data can be collected using the sensors that have been installed. For example, Weather conditions, animal health, crop conditions, and so on are examples of such data. Therefore, farmers can simply review and analyze data in one spot to make the best decision possible.</p>
</li>
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation" style="text-align: justify;">Risk Reduction: When farmers understand what problems are happening with their production process, they can grasp the situation in the future and forecast some issues that may occur. Moreover, farmers also can use the collected data to increase the sale activities and improve their working process to save time and money.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation" style="text-align: justify;">Reduce Resources: Plenty of IoT solutions are focused on optimizing the use of resources—water, energy, land. For example, precision farming, as mentioned above, using IoT relies on the data collected from various sensors in the field, which helps farmers accurately allocate just enough resources within one plant.</p>
</li>
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation" style="text-align: justify;">Improve Product Quality: The application of IoT in agriculture can help farmers improve their product quality by using soil and crop sensors, aerial drone monitoring, and farm mapping. As a result, farmers better understand detailed dependencies between the conditions and the quality of the crops, which boosts the nutritional worth of the items by using connected systems.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 style="text-align: justify;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-180ff46f-7fff-3389-c50c-dcacdc847069">Conclusion</b></h2>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">In conclusion, markets will grow and collapse, disruptive business models will emerge or die, but people will always need food and drink to maintain their life. For this reason, the development of such areas as food production and farming activities will always be a priority, especially given the dynamics we observe in the world today. Therefore, IoT used in agriculture has a promising future as a driving force of efficiency, sustainability, and scalability in this industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;"><em><strong>Rikkeisoft hopes you found these IoT solutions for Agriculture&nbsp;helpful for your company to apply. If the post inspired you to consider taking similar steps, contact us via&nbsp; contact@rikkeisoft.com, and we will prepare an IoT solution for you! To see more technology blogs, let’s dig in&nbsp;<a href="https://rikkeisoft.com/en/">https://rikkeisoft.com/en/</a>&nbsp;</strong></em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/577/iot-solution-for-the-new-4-0-agriculture-2/">IoT solution for the new 4.0 Agriculture</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>More than smart city: IoT is changing the world</title>
		<link>https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/576/more-than-smart-city-iot-is-changing-the-world-5/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chitv@rikkeisoft.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 02:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Lastest Thinking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rikkeisoft.com/2021/10/14/more-than-smart-city-iot-is-changing-the-world-5/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Over the past few years, IoT has become one of the most important technologies of the 21st century, and it has a lot of potentials. Now that we can connect everyday objects—kitchen appliances, cars, thermostats, baby monitors—to the internet via embedded devices, seamless communication is possible between people, processes, and things. The potential of IoT [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/576/more-than-smart-city-iot-is-changing-the-world-5/">More than smart city: IoT is changing the world</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Over the past few years, IoT has become one of the most important technologies of the 21st century, and it has a lot of potentials. Now that we can connect everyday objects—kitchen appliances, cars, thermostats, baby monitors—to the internet via embedded devices, seamless communication is possible between people, processes, and things. The potential of IoT will unlock the future opportunities of every industrial area and, furthermore, changing the world. This blog will illustrate the potential of IoT and how IoT creates a smart world.&nbsp;&nbsp;</strong></p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="900" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/%E1%BA%A2nh-02-02.png" width="1600"></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">With the advancement of IoT technology, nations worldwide are implementing and constructing smart cities, which can be seen in developed cities such as Korea’s Busan, Singapore, and China’s Shenzhen. The government has used IoT to construct smart cities, according to the study IoT-Enabled Smart Cities: Evolution and Outlook of MDPI 2021, specifically as follows:&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation" style="text-align: justify;">The Busan smart city, the second-most populous city in South Korea, the Busan smart city initiated its second phase project to establish an open smart city platform based on global IoT/M2M standards. The second phase of the smart city project was started in 2016 with government funds to achieve interoperability between Service, Platform, Network, Device, and Security ecosystems. The smart city introduced seven experimental applications in 2017: Smart street lights, Smart crosswalks, Smart parking, Building energy management, Lost child prevention, etc.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation" style="text-align: justify;">The Smart Nation and Digital Governance Group (SNDGG), which directly reports to the Prime Minister’s Office, oversees the planning and execution of smart city projects [23]. The government operates various smart city R&amp;D projects through many subordinate organizations. Of particular note are the AI-focused ones, including the AI Singapore Project, which is being conducted in collaboration with the National University of Singapore (NUS). The Singaporean government has established six smart city visions such as Smart Urban Mobility, Smart Nation Sensor Platform, National Digital Identity, etc.</p>
</li>
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation" style="text-align: justify;">The smart city in Shenzhen, China, aims to strengthen the existing manufacturing industry while connecting it to the advantages offered by the digital industry. The smart city plan established by the city in 2018 includes public services (healthcare, education, community, and weather), city management services (safety, transportation, operation, and water quality), and economic development services (industry, digital economy, and industrial complexes) with Water quality management, Smart industrial complexes, and public safety.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="768" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/%E1%BA%A2nh-02-03.png" width="1600"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">As IoT becomes more widespread in the marketplace, the future of IoT has the potential to be limitless (quote) As a result, many fields benefit from IoT, such as manufacturing, automotive, retails, education, healthcare, transportation, logistics, etc. To be more specific, The automotive industry stands to realize significant advantages from the use of IoT applications. Sensors can identify approaching equipment failure in cars currently on the road and inform the driver with facts and advice, in addition to the benefits of using IoT on manufacturing lines. Automotive manufacturers and suppliers may learn more about how to keep automobiles operating, and car owners informed thanks to aggregated data acquired by IoT-based applications. Furthermore, in the Healthcare field, there are some IoT applications such as Glucose monitoring and Heart-rate monitoring, which allow users to better manage their health and respond to their requirements. In the future, the potential of IoT is predicted to fix the outdated data access, focus on 5G and the super data-center trend and solve the risk of security.&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">In conclusion, the IoT-enabled new world is quickly changing. Now is the time to get ready. IoT promises to decrease waste, expense, and annoyance while boosting efficiency, thanks to these fantastic prospects. But maybe the most interesting aspect is that IoT allows us to live in a cleaner environment while also allowing us to work more effectively and with greater quality. However, additional study and creative thinking are required to overcome the security and power consumption issues brought by unrivaled IoT connections and, at the same time, dubious IoT security.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/576/more-than-smart-city-iot-is-changing-the-world-5/">More than smart city: IoT is changing the world</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>3 challenges of AI that Vietnam IT Companies have to face</title>
		<link>https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/492/3-challenges-of-ai-that-vietnam-it-companies-have-to-face/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chitv@rikkeisoft.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 08:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Lastest Thinking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rikkeisoft.com/2021/09/24/3-challenges-of-ai-that-vietnam-it-companies-have-to-face/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#160; AI is a technology that can revolutionize manufacturing industries, healthcare, space exploration, and more. As a result, artificial intelligence is growing and gaining popularity at an excellent rate. This growing popularity of AI has urged several businesses to invest in developing and researching different AI applications like robots and automated cars. However, it is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/492/3-challenges-of-ai-that-vietnam-it-companies-have-to-face/">3 challenges of AI that Vietnam IT Companies have to face</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><meta charset="utf-8"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-9662e299-7fff-9446-ccb8-bd1d26dd422f">AI is a technology that can revolutionize manufacturing industries, healthcare, space exploration, and more. As a result, artificial intelligence is growing and gaining popularity at an excellent rate. This growing popularity of AI has urged several businesses to invest in developing and researching different AI applications like robots and automated cars.</b></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-9662e299-7fff-9446-ccb8-bd1d26dd422f">However, it is important to note that AI is still facing some challenges. Here are some of the common challenges that most Vietnam IT companies face when implementing Artificial Intelligence.</b></p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="533" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/210924%204AI_1.png" width="1600"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">As most of you are probably aware, AI systems are driven and developed by leveraging quality data. Therefore, the difficulty of accurate data collecting and quality control and the expense of labeling data are the most challenging aspects for every AI business wherever in the globe. Vinfast, for example, is a major artificial intelligence application company in Vietnam. Vinfast is Vietnam&#8217;s sole autonomous vehicle research and development center. Vinfast has invested a lot of time and money into putting together a fleet of cars that can go around the streets and snap photographs in a range of time and weather situations.</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">According to Nguyen Minh Tan &#8211; Vice Managing Director of Rikkei AI</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">&#8220;An AI product is a synthesis of many different materials, and data is one of the essential components. According to statistics, up to 80% of AI product development time is spent on data-related processing.”&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">In addition, training AI is similar to educating a child. AI can learn successfully if the correct data is used to train it. In contrast, if we teach AI with incorrect data, it will learn incorrectly. Furthermore, when heterogeneous data is used at an inaccurate moment, the AI becomes confused. Therefore, the privacy and security of data collecting and training for AI should be paid attention to; the more data appropriately utilized for training, the smarter the AI becomes and the more precisely it can recognize.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="533" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/210924%204AI_3(1).png" width="1600"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Here is one of the most critical challenges in AI, one that has kept researchers on edge for AI services in companies and start-ups. These companies might be boasting of above 90% accuracy, but humans can do better in all of these scenarios. For example, let our model predict whether the image is of a dog or a cat. The human can predict the correct output nearly every time, mopping up a stunning accuracy of above 99%.</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">For a deep learning model to perform a similar performance would require unprecedented finetuning, hyperparameter optimization, a large dataset, and a well-defined and accurate algorithm, along with robust computing power, uninterrupted training on train data, and testing on test data. That sounds like a lot of work, and it’s actually a hundred times more difficult than it sounds.</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">AI companies can avoid doing all the hard work by using a service provider to train specific deep learning models using pre-trained models. They are trained on millions of images and are fine-tuned for maximum accuracy, but the real problem is that they continue to show errors and would really struggle to reach human-level performance.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">&nbsp;</h3>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="533" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/210924%204AI_2.png" width="1600"></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">The amount of power these power-hungry algorithms use is a factor keeping most developers away. Machine Learning and Deep Learning are the stepping stones of this Artificial Intelligence, and they demand an ever-increasing number of cores and GPUs to work efficiently. There are various domains where we have ideas and knowledge to implement deep learning frameworks such as asteroid tracking, healthcare deployment, tracing of cosmic bodies, and much more.</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">They require a supercomputer’s computing power, and yes, supercomputers aren’t cheap. Although developers work on AI systems more effectively due to the availability of Cloud Computing and parallel processing systems, they come at a price. Not everyone can afford that with an increase in the inflow of unprecedented amounts of data and rapidly increasing complex algorithms.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-9662e299-7fff-9446-ccb8-bd1d26dd422f">Conclusion</b></h2>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Businesses will have to familiarize themselves with AI, which will help them understand how AI works. There is no denying that implementing AI in businesses can have several challenges, and you will start noticing these challenges when creating an AI strategy for your business. However, adopting a step-by-step and strategic approach will simplify the process of AI implementation to a certain level.</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">If you’re interested in updating more about technical knowledge, please stay tuned for the new Rikkeisoft blog!&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/492/3-challenges-of-ai-that-vietnam-it-companies-have-to-face/">3 challenges of AI that Vietnam IT Companies have to face</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vice Managing Director of Rikkei AI: To compete in the AI game, companies must own the huge data resources</title>
		<link>https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/488/vice-managing-director-of-rikkei-ai-to-compete-in-the-ai-game-companies-must-own-the-huge-data-resources/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chitv@rikkeisoft.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 02:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Lastest Thinking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rikkeisoft.com/2021/09/11/vice-managing-director-of-rikkei-ai-to-compete-in-the-ai-game-companies-must-own-the-huge-data-resources/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#160; AI is currently being used to accelerate progress in vital fields such as health, agriculture, finance, and transport. However, good data sources are essential for AI to further develop evenly across areas and regions. Data availability is the key for training AI systems, with products and services rapidly moving from pattern recognition and insight [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/488/vice-managing-director-of-rikkei-ai-to-compete-in-the-ai-game-companies-must-own-the-huge-data-resources/">Vice Managing Director of Rikkei AI: To compete in the AI game, companies must own the huge data resources</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><meta charset="utf-8"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">AI is currently being used to accelerate progress in vital fields such as health, agriculture, finance, and transport. However, good data sources are essential for AI to further develop evenly across areas and regions. Data availability is the key for training AI systems, with products and services rapidly moving from pattern recognition and insight generation to more sophisticated forecasting techniques and, thus, better decision making.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-4c0858ce-7fff-24b1-f9ea-90ac18cd6137">&nbsp;</b></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Businesses need to own a huge data warehouse to join this AI competition to capture and lead the latest technology trend. Some Vietnam technology pillars such as FPT, Viettel, VinAI, and VNG have built their huge data warehouses to approach future trends. As a part of Vietnam technology leaders, Rikkeisoft is not out of the AI game with a vast audio data warehouse for the “Speech to text”&nbsp; product. Besides, for readers to have a multi-view about the role of data in the development of AI; Rikkeisoft had a small interview with Mr. Nguyen Minh Tan (Vice Managing Director of Rikkei AI-&nbsp; the “cradle” of almost all AI products and projects of Rikkeisoft), let’s stay tuned!&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="533" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/1_Mesa%20de%20trabajo%201.png" width="1600"></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">AI stands for Artificial Intelligence, which means artificial intelligence. People are always trying to think and develop algorithms to make computers smarter. Artificial intelligence was conceived in the 1950s. However, due to the limit of computing power, computers at that time could only do pre-defined coding tasks. The current era is the age of artificial intelligence. Computer processing capability continues to grow, and computer costs fall, allowing more people to access advanced technology, resulting in AI becoming more widely recognized and used in practice.</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="533" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/q4_Mesa%20de%20trabajo%201.png" width="1600"></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Many opinions argued data is the new source of black gold of the 21st century, not oil. An AI product is a synthesis of many different materials, and data is one of the essential components. According to statistics, up to 80% of AI product development time is spent on data-related processing. Training AI is similar to educating a child. AI can learn successfully if the correct data is used to train it. In contrast, if we teach AI with incorrect data, it will learn incorrectly. When heterogeneous data is used at an inaccurate moment, the AI becomes confused. The more data appropriately utilized for training, the smarter the AI becomes and the more precisely it can recognize.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><meta charset="utf-8"></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">There is no doubt that large technology companies such as Google and Microsoft and self-driving vehicle companies like Tesla, Hyundai, and Toyota have heavily invested in data to remain ahead of the competition. For example, hundreds of thousands of hours of audio data were used to train Google&#8217;s speech recognition engine. Likewise, Tesla uses millions of real photographs to teach its self-driving cars.</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Companies that specialize in data labeling appear to be following the AI trend as well. In addition, data labeling technologies that are quicker and more accurate are also being developed. As a result, many of these businesses have gone on to become unicorn start-ups.&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="533" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/Q3_Mesa%20de%20trabajo%201.png" width="1600"></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">As we all know, Rikkeisoft&#8217;s Speech To Text with the core technology is a voice recognition solution deployed to the National Assembly and several ministries, provinces, agencies, and other government entities. Although Speech Recognition technology has a wide range of applications, only a few firms in Vietnam hold it. Some big names such as Viettel, FPT, VNG, and VinGroup are all significant players. So, why do so few firms take the risk of participating in this game? Because, in addition to the resources of buildings, equipment infrastructure, and technical staff capable of training AI, a large amount of speech sound data is required to create this technology. It costs a lot of money to collect and categorize this audio data. Not all firms are willing to accept financial risks, especially when the feasibility of mastering technology and product output is uncertain. We may claim that Rikkeisoft is fortunate in having the vision and a great technological team since it possesses one of the most significant technologies.</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="992" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/anh%20ai%201_Mesa%20de%20trabajo%201.png" width="1600"></p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img alt="" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/q5_Mesa%20de%20trabajo%201.png"></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><meta charset="utf-8"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">The difficulty of accurate data collecting and quality control and the expense of labeling data are the most challenging aspects of producing data wherever in the globe. Vinfast, for example, is a major artificial intelligence application company in Vietnam. Vinfast is Vietnam&#8217;s sole autonomous vehicle research and development center. Vinfast has invested a lot of time and money into putting together a fleet of cars that can go around the streets and snap photographs in a range of time and weather situations.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Rikkeisoft has been struggled to discover acoustic data sources that match reality, variety in content, geography, age, and gender when developing the Speech-To-Text product. When each person&#8217;s capacity to hear and comprehend is varied, data labeling might be challenging. People in this region, in particular, find it difficult to hear and adequately capture the sounds spoken by others. Rikkeisoft has studied and developed Rikano, a professional data labeling tool, to meet the need for internal data labeling and new service development. Rikano was created by using and referencing the features of many other labeling tools around the world. It can label the most common types of data, such as images, sounds, and text while making it simple for users to manage progress, quality of work, productivity, and the working history of each project participant. As a result, Rikano plays a vital role in Rikkeisoft&#8217;s data labeling service&#8217;s development strategy.</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="533" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/q6_Mesa%20de%20trabajo%201.png" width="1600"></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><meta charset="utf-8"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Businesses are becoming more interested in AI as they better understand the benefits it may provide. As a result, all data connected to the business&#8217;s activities will be restored to assist AI construction in optimizing operations.</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Another AI trend is creating algorithms to prevent data labeling, a labor-intensive task that is likely to be controlled by the emotional element or the human factor. However, this is still a future issue.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/488/vice-managing-director-of-rikkei-ai-to-compete-in-the-ai-game-companies-must-own-the-huge-data-resources/">Vice Managing Director of Rikkei AI: To compete in the AI game, companies must own the huge data resources</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Five fields that AI might be good for</title>
		<link>https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/569/five-fields-that-ai-might-be-good-for-3/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chitv@rikkeisoft.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 09:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Lastest Thinking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rikkeisoft.com/2021/08/12/five-fields-that-ai-might-be-good-for-3/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Artificial Intelligence (AI) certainly makes people&#8217;s lives more efficient, and it powers many programs and services that help us do daily activities, from simple pleasures such as creating funny suggestions for your comment on Facebook to complicated tasks like developing self-driving cars.&#160; In this post, let’s dig into What positive aspects that AI can create [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/569/five-fields-that-ai-might-be-good-for-3/">Five fields that AI might be good for</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr"><b id="docs-internal-guid-41b613ac-7fff-06c8-9f54-11f15434ea9c">Artificial Intelligence (AI) certainly makes people&#8217;s lives more efficient, and it powers many programs and services that help us do daily activities, from simple pleasures such as creating funny suggestions for your comment on Facebook to complicated tasks like developing self-driving cars.&nbsp; In this post, let’s dig into What positive aspects that AI can create for human life in the five following industries!&nbsp;</b></p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="1200" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/210810%20linkedin-01.png" width="1043"></p>
<ol>
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<h3 dir="ltr" role="presentation"><b id="docs-internal-guid-41b613ac-7fff-06c8-9f54-11f15434ea9c">Healthcare</b></h3>
</li>
</ol>
<p dir="ltr">Across the healthcare industry, AI is changing the way clinical providers make decisions. More than ever, it&#8217;s playing a key role in clinical decision support as it delivers data to providers to aid in diagnosing, treatment planning, and population health management.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">For example, by detecting keywords and analyzing voices, an Emergency AI Call Center can recognize a patient’s symptoms during the call faster and more frequently than medical dispatchers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ol start="2">
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<h3 dir="ltr" role="presentation"><b id="docs-internal-guid-41b613ac-7fff-06c8-9f54-11f15434ea9c">Transportation&nbsp;</b></h3>
</li>
</ol>
<p dir="ltr">The transportation industry has begun applying artificial intelligence in critical tasks such as self-driving cars, traffic management, where safety and reliability are major concerns.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">For example, self-driving cars are no longer a dream; many companies like Tesla, Mercedes, and BMW have released autonomous cars that bring lots of benefits, such as reducing traffic accidents by identifying dangerous situations.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ol start="3">
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<h3 dir="ltr" role="presentation"><b id="docs-internal-guid-41b613ac-7fff-06c8-9f54-11f15434ea9c">Agriculture</b></h3>
</li>
</ol>
<p dir="ltr">The power of AI can be used for ensuring healthier food by minimizing the use of fertilizers, pesticides, and irrigation while improving productivity and reducing the impact on the environment.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">For details, Plantix &#8211; the German-based tech startup, by taking photos of the plants, this app can help farmers identify nutrient deficiencies in soil, including plant pests and diseases; therefore, they can also get an idea to use fertilizer, which helps improve harvest quality.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ol start="4">
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<h3 dir="ltr" role="presentation"><b id="docs-internal-guid-41b613ac-7fff-06c8-9f54-11f15434ea9c">Customer service</b></h3>
</li>
</ol>
<p dir="ltr">The traditional customer service method can only handle one customer service call or problem at a time. However, the use of AI allows customer service teams to handle more requirements at the same time, increasing customer satisfaction.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chatbots, for example, can handle multiple queries at once. This is an efficient way for businesses that have busy call centers and struggle with wait times.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ol start="5">
<li aria-level="1" dir="ltr">
<h3 dir="ltr" role="presentation"><b id="docs-internal-guid-41b613ac-7fff-06c8-9f54-11f15434ea9c">Recruitment</b></h3>
</li>
</ol>
<p dir="ltr">With the advent of <meta charset="utf-8"><b id="docs-internal-guid-f3b92f72-7fff-2b5d-14ae-1cc7e8420535">&nbsp;</b>AI for recruiting, the process of recruitment is more standardized. Moreover, the candidates approaching process taken over by the recruiters is changing too.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For example, using an AI-powered Applicant Tracking System (ATS) to scan through hundreds of CVs and look for keywords or phrases to find appropriate candidates.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">If the post inspired you to consider taking similar steps, contact us via&nbsp; contact@rikkeisoft.com, and we will prepare a solution for you! To see more technology blogs, let’s dig in <a href="https://rikkeisoft.com/en/">https://rikkeisoft.com/en/</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">#Rikkeisoft #Rikkeiservice #technology #RikkeiAI #Artificialintelligience #innovative #humanlife&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/569/five-fields-that-ai-might-be-good-for-3/">Five fields that AI might be good for</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>5 common mistakes of digital transformation</title>
		<link>https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/484/5-common-mistakes-of-digital-transformation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chitv@rikkeisoft.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Lastest Thinking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rikkeisoft.com/2021/08/02/5-common-mistakes-of-digital-transformation/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Most businesses have understood that they need to go through a digital transformation if they want to stay competitive. However, many companies don&#8217;t know how to get their digital activities up and running successfully.&#160; &#160; In this post, Rikkeisoft will now take you through the five most common mistakes we see with digital transformations to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/484/5-common-mistakes-of-digital-transformation/">5 common mistakes of digital transformation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Most businesses have understood that they need to go through a digital transformation if they want to stay competitive. However, many companies don&rsquo;t know how to get their digital activities up and running successfully.&nbsp;</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">&nbsp;</p>
<p><meta charset="utf-8" /></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">In this post, Rikkeisoft will now take you through the five most common mistakes we see with digital transformations to give you an idea of what to avoid.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation" style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size:22px;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-81944049-7fff-cf94-9b0f-d15808b45010">1. The biggest digital transformation mistake: Thinking digital is the destination</b></span></p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="1200" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/210730%20LINKEDIN%201%20(1).jpg" width="1200" /></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">The first and most important thing for digital leaders to realize is that digital transformation is a process, not a destination. Digital practices will allow the organization to streamline processes and deliver results if done right. However, they won&rsquo;t change the core processes of the organization or fix loopholes beyond their scope.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation"><span style="font-size:22px;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-81944049-7fff-cf94-9b0f-d15808b45010">2. Thinking digitalization and digital transformation are the same&nbsp;</b></span></p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="1200" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/210730%20LINKEDIN%202.jpg" width="1200" /></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Digital transformation is a long-term process, including digitization and digitalization. As a result, digital leaders have to distinguish between these definitions clearly. To create the long-term goals of digital transformation, companies need to understand how the digital transformation process works.&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation"><span style="font-size:22px;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-81944049-7fff-cf94-9b0f-d15808b45010">3. Thinking that digital transformation is a one-time process</b></span></p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="1200" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/210730%20LINKEDIN%203%20(1).jpg" width="1200" /></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">A major digital transformation mistake assumes that it is a one-time initiative, which will last forever. The goal of digital transformation should be to create an organization that is adaptable and eager to adopt relevant digital solutions as they become available. Leaders should foster an environment that encourages experimentation and curiosity, allowing them to stay one step ahead of the next disruptor.</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation"><span style="font-size:22px;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-81944049-7fff-cf94-9b0f-d15808b45010">4. Expecting unrealistic results from day 1</b></span></p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="1200" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/210730%20LINKEDIN%204%20(1).jpg" width="1200" /></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">As we have been mentioning, digital transformation is a process. It will take time, effort, and multiple risks before it gets to the results stage. It would be an ignorant digital transformation mistake to expect results from the day the process has started. Digital transformation is done keeping the larger picture in consideration instead of short-term wins and gains.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation"><span style="font-size:22px;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-81944049-7fff-cf94-9b0f-d15808b45010">5. Choosing the wrong digital partners</b></span></p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="1200" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/210730%20LINKEDIN%205%20(1).jpg" width="1200" /></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Digital leaders should be careful to choose digital partners and not digital vendors, as their choice will determine the success of their digital transformation process. Digital partners should not be chosen by just taking cost or past relationships into account. Instead, a full analysis of various factors should be undertaken to choose the right digital partners.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Rikkeisoft hopes you found these digital transformation mistakes helpful for your company to avoid. If the post inspired you to consider taking similar steps, contact us via&nbsp; contact@rikkeisoft.com, and we will prepare a solution for you! To see more technology blogs, let&rsquo;s dig in <a href="https://rikkeisoft.com/en/">https://rikkeisoft.com/en/</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">#Rikkeisoft #digitaltransformation #digitalworld #common #mistakes #technologypost #vietnam #innovative&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/lastest-thinking/484/5-common-mistakes-of-digital-transformation/">5 common mistakes of digital transformation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
