<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Newsroom &#8211; Rikkeisoft &#8211; Your trusted IT provider</title>
	<atom:link href="https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://rikkeisoft.com</link>
	<description>Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 09:07:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.7</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The massive growth of IT Vietnamese company in global market – Rikkei Japan opens a base in Osaka</title>
		<link>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/460/the-massive-growth-of-it-vietnamese-company-in-global-market-rikkei-japan-opens-a-base-in-osaka/</link>
					<comments>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/460/the-massive-growth-of-it-vietnamese-company-in-global-market-rikkei-japan-opens-a-base-in-osaka/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chitv@rikkeisoft.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Newsroom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rikkeisoft.com/2021/12/02/the-massive-growth-of-it-vietnamese-company-in-global-market-rikkei-japan-opens-a-base-in-osaka/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Article on Kahm Japan: &#160; About the company launched by young graduates of Ritsumeikan and Keio &#8211; What is Rikkei? April 6, 2012 &#8211; Rikkeisoft was launched by a team of only 5 people. The company name, Rikkei, is derived from the alma maters of the chairman (Ritsumeikan) and other board members (Keio). The chairman, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/460/the-massive-growth-of-it-vietnamese-company-in-global-market-rikkei-japan-opens-a-base-in-osaka/">The massive growth of IT Vietnamese company in global market – Rikkei Japan opens a base in Osaka</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-size:22px;"><span style="color:#3498db;"><strong>Article on Kahm Japan:</strong></span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><meta charset="utf-8"><span style="font-size:18px;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-efa61643-7fff-b9c0-ec4d-2a96dec2bad8">About the company launched by young graduates of Ritsumeikan and Keio &#8211; What is Rikkei?</b></span></p>
<p>April 6, 2012 &#8211; Rikkeisoft was launched by a team of only 5 people. The company name, Rikkei, is derived from the alma maters of the chairman (Ritsumeikan) and other board members (Keio). The chairman, Ta Son Tung, on one occasion had the opportunity to attend international conferences in both France and Britain while he still was studying in Japan. But Vietnamese citizens are required to get visas for both, so by the time his visa arrived, it was too late; he could only go to France. His Japanese friend, by contrast, could go to both without needing a visa. At that moment, it became apparent that Vietnam was still a poor country; this despite Vietnam being a country with a multitude of young people and many, many excellent engineers. Together with Huy, a classmate, they created a startup, Rikkeisoft, to prove that good things could be made in Vietnam and to show Vietnam’s power to the world.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="901" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/1(3).png" width="600"></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><meta charset="utf-8"><meta charset="utf-8">Since its establishment in April, 2012, Rikkeisoft has grown into a company of more than 1200 employees. Based in Hanoi, Rikkeisoft has also been able to build development bases in Da Nang and Ho Chi Minh City. They’ve received multiple awards, among them the “Sao Khue Award” for excellent software and information technology services and the “Vietnam IT Enterprise Top 50” as awarded by the Vietnam IT Association. Rikkeisoft aims to reach 10,000 employees by 2024 with 1,000 among them working within Rikkei Japan. They also aim to enable global human resource exchange and global environment building from the borders of both Japan and Vietnam.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="487" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/2(2).png" width="730"></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-size:18px;"><strong>Rikkei Inc &#8211; The Japanese subsidiary:</strong></span></p>
<p>In 2016, Rikkei Inc was established and since then, it has grown to 120 employees. Rikkei Inc has grown dramatically since being founded and was selected as one of the “Best Venture 100” companies in 2020. In January 2020, Rikkei Inc opened a branch in Osaka.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="521" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/3.png" width="700"></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-size:18px;"><strong>Impressions/requests about the environment for startups in Osaka:</strong></span></p>
<p>The Rikkei Osaka office was launched in order to strengthen relationships with customers in the Kansai area and expand its operations. They aim to reach 50 employees by the end of 2020 and have 400 by 2024. Rikkei Osaka is working with universities in the Kansai area, also active in the developing human resources, and conducting joint research. They are working to cooperate and contribute to the activities of the Kansai Vietnamese Association.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Many Japanese find it difficult to manage Vietnamese developers. There are, after all, differences in communication and culture. However, according to Osaka’s President Nakamura: “There are no differences as around me the Japanese and Vietnamese are close comrades. We value commitment with each other, so we always talk one-on-one with each other, face-to-face, so we can build a closer relationship.&#8221;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="466" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/4.png" width="700"></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>To build these close relationships, Nakamura is always careful to make the atmosphere as bright and easy to talk in as possible. Not just valusing communication through words, the office makes a point of using smiles and good gestures as effective communication methods. They want to be careful to make an environment where when something good happens, they can praise it with a huge and genuine reaction.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>“Rikkei employees working in Japan, come to Japan, learn Japanese, and meet every day with Japanese customers working in the IT industry. Even if there is something wrong with their Japanese, they still have the same ideas as the Japanese do. They’re happy if they’re able to thank their customers and sad when they’re unable to achieve customer satisfaction. When Rikkei employees join a customer’s team and I get to directly receive a customer’s evaluations: That is the time I am most happy.”</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-size:18px;"><strong>Rikkei’s strength:</strong></span></p>
<p>Rikkei’s strength lay in the breadth of their experience within the software development industry. During the early years, they developed web systems and smartphone applications, but they were able to branch out into cutting-edge fields such as game development, business and core systems, IoT, AI and Robotics. It is these last two fields in particular that Rikkeisoft has a prominent track record with: Rikkei AI and Rikkei Robotics are specialized companies established for the purpose of strengthening their knowledge in these areas.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>In addition, at the three offices in Vietnam, customers are not just able to keep in direct contact with resident and pilot development projects or human resource development for large-scale projects offshore, but also able to develop a friendly long-term relationship between the companies. Since Rikkei’s growth is for the sake of its customers, the main goal is “Growing together with the customer”.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-size:18px;"><strong>What makes Rikkei different from other Vietnamese companies?</strong></span></p>
<p>“Rikkei’s employees are generally young with a strong sense of vitality. They have a flat organizational structure and are actively engaged with both internal projects and events. They’re not the type to wait to be told to do something, rather being industrious and taking the initiative. This is why Rikkei’s are able to build such powerful momentum when they start something. The speed that they make decisions and solve problems is why they are appealing to me as an organization.” Words for the youth of both Japan and Vietnam Nakamura: “This is just what I want, but I would like to do more Japanese training, so that Japanese business customs and culture can be better understood. It is something that I think is very important for building a system development team.”</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Even if they are staff from different companies, they’re still the same team when working on the same project. If they’re on the same team, they can help each when they’re in trouble and when they’re successful, they can be happy and laugh together. Otherwise, without these experiences, the project is repetitive work and becomes difficult.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Yet, even when times are tough, there are scenes of laughter, and if someone says something funny, the point of laughter will be the same even for the Vietnamese. It’s important that customers and team members learn to get along through such experiences, so I’d like it if somehow we could get to the point where we’re able say jokes in Japanese to each other. I hope that when they return to Vietnam, that they will bring back their experiences and memories of Japan as valuable assets.”</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><meta charset="utf-8"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><span style="font-size:22px;"><span style="color:#3498db;"><strong>News on Inovation Osaka:</strong></span></span></p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="667" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/Copy%20of%20IMG_7131.JPG" width="500"></p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Rikkeisoft Vietnam was founded in 2012 by Vietnamese entrepreneurs who had studied in Japan. The company was named for both Ritsumeikan, the university that the Chairman and President attended, and Keio, the university that the other staff members attended.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In order to expand Rikkeisoft’s reach in the Japanese market, Rikkei Japan was established in 2016. It currently has more than 120 employees. On January 1, 2020, Rikkei was selected for Japan’s 100 Best Venture Companies for its success and opened a branch office in Osaka.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Rikkeisoft Osaka office plans to build and strengthen its relationships with customers and universities, expand its activities, and engage fully in human resource development and joint research in the Kansai region. Furthermore, it is committed to cooperating with the Vietnamese Association of Kansai.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Quite a few Japanese find it difficult to manage Vietnamese developers. Certainly, there are differences in communication and culture. However, Osaka Office Director Mr. Nakamura says, “In my mind, there is no difference between the Japanese and Vietnamese staff because we are both members of the same group of companies. We value communication with our members, and I talk to employees face-to-face every day to build close relationships.”</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In other words, our mission is to create a startup environment where foreign entrepreneurs who have studied in Japan and established a business in their home country, will see the value of Japan, and the Osaka and Kansai area, when they consider their next business location.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/460/the-massive-growth-of-it-vietnamese-company-in-global-market-rikkei-japan-opens-a-base-in-osaka/">The massive growth of IT Vietnamese company in global market – Rikkei Japan opens a base in Osaka</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/460/the-massive-growth-of-it-vietnamese-company-in-global-market-rikkei-japan-opens-a-base-in-osaka/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rikkeisoft won the 2020 Top 10 Vietnam Companies Award for AI/IoT and Outsourcing</title>
		<link>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/280/rikkeisoft-won-the-2020-top-10-vietnam-companies-award-for-ai-iot-and-outsourcing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chitv@rikkeisoft.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 04:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Newsroom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rikkeisoft.com/?p=280</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>14th of December, 2020 &#8211; Rikkeisoft won the 2020 Top 10 Vietnam Companies Award for AI/IoT and Outsourcing. In previous years known as the Vietnam Top 50+10 Leading Companies Award, the Top 10 Vietnam ICT Companies Award is presented to companies evaluated and recognized as reputable and outstanding in their fields. Every company that wins [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/280/rikkeisoft-won-the-2020-top-10-vietnam-companies-award-for-ai-iot-and-outsourcing/">Rikkeisoft won the 2020 Top 10 Vietnam Companies Award for AI/IoT and Outsourcing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>14th of December, 2020 &#8211; Rikkeisoft won the 2020 Top 10 Vietnam Companies Award for AI/IoT and Outsourcing.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="775" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/7-1024x775.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-269" srcset="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/7-1024x775.jpg 1024w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/7-300x227.jpg 300w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/7-768x581.jpg 768w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/7-1536x1163.jpg 1536w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/7.jpg 1585w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>In previous years known as the Vietnam Top 50+10 Leading Companies Award, the Top 10 Vietnam ICT Companies Award is presented to companies evaluated and recognized as reputable and outstanding in their fields. Every company that wins an award is listed in a catalogue written in Vietnamese, English, and Japanese, which lists the services available from the company as well as other notable information. Rikkeisoft has won the award every year since 2014, but 2020 marks the first time that the award is being presented based on different categories.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The award is presented by the Vietnamese Software &amp; IT Services Association (Vinasa). Established in 2002, Vinasa is a national association composed of 270 different member companies, who work together to help develop the Vietnamese software industry. Vinasa members account for 65% of all professional programmers in Vietnam and 75% of all domestic software production.</p>



<p>The award for outsourcing, as presented to our own Phan Thi Lan Anh, commemorates our productive work with clients all over the world. While Japan still makes up our largest client load, 2020 saw us being able to focus more on other countries such as Korea, Australia, Singapore, France, and the United States. In the years to come, we hope to see other countries like Germany, Canada, New Zealand, and more added to the list.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="683" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/8-1024x683.png" alt="" class="wp-image-274" srcset="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/8-1024x683.png 1024w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/8-300x200.png 300w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/8-768x512.png 768w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/8-1536x1024.png 1536w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/8.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>The award for AI/IoT, received by Rikkei AI Director Dang Thai Hoa, was presented in celebration of our work in advancing the realm of Vietnamese robotics. Rikkei AI has spent much of 2020 developing many capable products, like eKYC or OCR systems, that have caught the attention of various news agencies around the country. Luna, our child education robot capable of teaching songs and stories, will be one of the first domestically produced Vietnamese robots in the entire country. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="683" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/9-1024x683.png" alt="" class="wp-image-275" srcset="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/9-1024x683.png 1024w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/9-300x200.png 300w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/9-768x512.png 768w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/9-1536x1024.png 1536w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/9.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>We are very proud to be receiving these awards as it commemorates our hard work and dedication in these respective fields. We look forward to bringing more top quality service to our customers in the years to come.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/280/rikkeisoft-won-the-2020-top-10-vietnam-companies-award-for-ai-iot-and-outsourcing/">Rikkeisoft won the 2020 Top 10 Vietnam Companies Award for AI/IoT and Outsourcing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A look back at the year 2020</title>
		<link>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/277/a-look-back-at-the-year-2020/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chitv@rikkeisoft.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 04:11:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Newsroom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rikkeisoft.com/?p=277</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We can surely speak for everyone when we say that 2020 was a very difficult year. Though it started out with promise, the Covid-19 pandemic forced us all to change our plans, leaving us with a year like no other. However, despite all the hardship, we were able to overcome and make a lot of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/277/a-look-back-at-the-year-2020/">A look back at the year 2020</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>We can surely speak for everyone when we say that 2020 was a very difficult year. Though it started out with promise, the Covid-19 pandemic forced us all to change our plans, leaving us with a year like no other. However, despite all the hardship, we were able to overcome and make a lot of happy memories that we’ll be able to take with us into the new year. As such, we’d like to take this final moment to thank our loyal customers and employees for their support and reflect on some of the milestones we achieved this year.</p>



<p><strong>1. We opened an office in Osaka</strong></p>



<p>We started the year on a positive note, moving into the vibrant downtown area of Chaya-machi. Opening a second Japanese office was no small feat, so we commemorated getting started in our fifth city by having a party at the InterContinental Osaka hotel. Led by Managing Director, Nakamura Keisuke, our Osaka office has already shown great signs of success and is expected to continue doing so as we move into the next year.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="707" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-1024x707.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-265" srcset="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-1024x707.jpg 1024w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-300x207.jpg 300w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-768x530.jpg 768w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-1536x1060.jpg 1536w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1.jpg 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><strong>2. Rikkeisoft anti-pandemic measures were a success!</strong></p>



<p>We were all forced into lockdown by the Covid-19, but that didn’t stop us from continuing to deliver quality products for all of our customers. Even while we were working from home, and especially during the second wave, we made extra sure to keep delivering on our promises, all while making sure we complied with social distancing. As a result, we were able to keep business running as usual.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="768" height="1024" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/2-768x1024.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-266" srcset="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/2-768x1024.jpg 768w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/2-225x300.jpg 225w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/2.jpg 900w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /></figure>



<p><strong>3. Rikkeisoft set a new mission, vision, and core values!</strong></p>



<p>We had to change ourselves, to not only deliver quality products to our partners, but also to do our part to build a better society. We decided to change ourselves to better take on new global markets! Aspiration, Improvement, Dedication, Innovation, Openness… These values will no doubt serve us well as we Raise Vietnamese Value and aim for the top spot in the world of Vietnamese technology.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="901" height="901" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/3.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-267" srcset="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/3.jpg 901w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/3-300x300.jpg 300w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/3-150x150.jpg 150w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/3-768x768.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 901px) 100vw, 901px" /></figure>



<p><strong>4.&nbsp;We raised 3 million USD in capital and transitioned from a privately-held limited company into a joint stock-held corporation</strong></p>



<p>When we started in 2012, we were just six friends working together in one cramped apartment. Now that we’d grown to a company of 1,200+, we needed to restructure ourselves to better function in the rapidly changing world of enterprises. In Vietnam, only a few local companies have the size necessary to call themselves a corporation and we are proud to be included on this exclusive list.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="577" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/4-1024x577.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-268" srcset="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/4-1024x577.jpg 1024w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/4-300x169.jpg 300w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/4-768x433.jpg 768w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/4.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><strong>5.&nbsp;We donated computers and rebuilt schools for minority communities!</strong></p>



<p>Our company ventured into the border regions to do our part to Raise Vietnamese Value. For example, in the storm-affected province of Quang Nam, we raised 400 million VND to help the local schools and towns get back on their feet. Not hoping to leave the people of Dien Bien out, we went to their province to donate computers, bringing them firmly into the 21st century. This isn’t to forget, finally, our trip to Ha Giang where we inaugurated a new school, which will help keep the children warm as they study in the cold winter months.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/5-1024x576.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-270" srcset="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/5-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/5-300x169.jpg 300w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/5-768x432.jpg 768w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/5-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/5.jpg 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><strong>6.&nbsp;We signed a strategic partnership with Oraichain!</strong></p>



<p>We secured the chance of a lifetime, when we signed up with the world’s first AI-powered Data Oracle Platform! Supporting them with our experts, 2021 is expected to be a year in which our two companies will take the blockchain world by storm! Our Chairman and CEO are both themselves getting involved, signing on as advisors to help them on their rise to stardom!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="712" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/6-1024x712.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-271" srcset="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/6-1024x712.jpg 1024w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/6-300x209.jpg 300w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/6-768x534.jpg 768w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/6-1536x1068.jpg 1536w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/6.jpg 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><strong>7.&nbsp;Rikkeisoft won at the 2020 Top 10 Vietnam ICT Companies!</strong></p>



<p>We were proud to be awarded VINASA’s prestigious awards for our work in the fields of Outsourcing and AI/IoT. 2020 was the first year that the awards were separated into different categories, so that we were recognized as leaders in these fields shows just how hard we’ve been working this year! We look forward to distinguishing ourselves again in next year’s edition!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="775" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/7-1024x775.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-269" srcset="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/7-1024x775.jpg 1024w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/7-300x227.jpg 300w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/7-768x581.jpg 768w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/7-1536x1163.jpg 1536w, https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/7.jpg 1585w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>All in all, 2020 proved to be a year unlike any other. For all its downs, it also had its ups, and there were lessons to be learned from each new memory we made. Our deepest gratitude for the last eight years of support and we hope to see you again in the years to come!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/277/a-look-back-at-the-year-2020/">A look back at the year 2020</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>4 challenges of AI that Vietnam IT Companies have to face</title>
		<link>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/572/4-challenges-of-ai-that-vietnam-it-companies-have-to-face/</link>
					<comments>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/572/4-challenges-of-ai-that-vietnam-it-companies-have-to-face/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chitv@rikkeisoft.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 08:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Newsroom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rikkeisoft.com/2021/09/24/4-challenges-of-ai-that-vietnam-it-companies-have-to-face/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AI is a technology that can revolutionize manufacturing industries, healthcare, space exploration, and more. As a result, artificial intelligence is growing and gaining popularity at an excellent rate. This growing popularity of AI has urged several businesses to invest in developing and researching different AI applications like robots and automated cars. However, it is important [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/572/4-challenges-of-ai-that-vietnam-it-companies-have-to-face/">4 challenges of AI that Vietnam IT Companies have to face</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-9662e299-7fff-9446-ccb8-bd1d26dd422f">AI is a technology that can revolutionize manufacturing industries, healthcare, space exploration, and more. As a result, artificial intelligence is growing and gaining popularity at an excellent rate. This growing popularity of AI has urged several businesses to invest in developing and researching different AI applications like robots and automated cars.</b></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-9662e299-7fff-9446-ccb8-bd1d26dd422f">However, it is important to note that AI is still facing some challenges. Here are some of the common challenges that most Vietnam IT companies face when implementing Artificial Intelligence.</b></p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="533" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/210924%204AI_1.png" width="1600" /></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">As most of you are probably aware, AI systems are driven and developed by leveraging quality data. Therefore, the difficulty of accurate data collecting and quality control and the expense of labeling data are the most challenging aspects for every AI business wherever in the globe. Vinfast, for example, is a major artificial intelligence application company in Vietnam. Vinfast is Vietnam&#39;s sole autonomous vehicle research and development center. Vinfast has invested a lot of time and money into putting together a fleet of cars that can go around the streets and snap photographs in a range of time and weather situations.</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">According to Nguyen Minh Tan &#8211; Vice Managing Director of Rikkei AI</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">&quot;An AI product is a synthesis of many different materials, and data is one of the essential components. According to statistics, up to 80% of AI product development time is spent on data-related processing.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">In addition, training AI is similar to educating a child. AI can learn successfully if the correct data is used to train it. In contrast, if we teach AI with incorrect data, it will learn incorrectly. Furthermore, when heterogeneous data is used at an inaccurate moment, the AI becomes confused. Therefore, the privacy and security of data collecting and training for AI should be paid attention to; the more data appropriately utilized for training, the smarter the AI becomes and the more precisely it can recognize.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="533" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/210924%204AI_3(1).png" width="1600" /></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Here is one of the most critical challenges in AI, one that has kept researchers on edge for AI services in companies and start-ups. These companies might be boasting of above 90% accuracy, but humans can do better in all of these scenarios. For example, let our model predict whether the image is of a dog or a cat. The human can predict the correct output nearly every time, mopping up a stunning accuracy of above 99%.</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">For a deep learning model to perform a similar performance would require unprecedented finetuning, hyperparameter optimization, a large dataset, and a well-defined and accurate algorithm, along with robust computing power, uninterrupted training on train data, and testing on test data. That sounds like a lot of work, and it&rsquo;s actually a hundred times more difficult than it sounds.</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">AI companies can avoid doing all the hard work by using a service provider to train specific deep learning models using pre-trained models. They are trained on millions of images and are fine-tuned for maximum accuracy, but the real problem is that they continue to show errors and would really struggle to reach human-level performance.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">&nbsp;</h3>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="533" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/210924%204AI_2.png" width="1600" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">The amount of power these power-hungry algorithms use is a factor keeping most developers away. Machine Learning and Deep Learning are the stepping stones of this Artificial Intelligence, and they demand an ever-increasing number of cores and GPUs to work efficiently. There are various domains where we have ideas and knowledge to implement deep learning frameworks such as asteroid tracking, healthcare deployment, tracing of cosmic bodies, and much more.</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">They require a supercomputer&rsquo;s computing power, and yes, supercomputers aren&rsquo;t cheap. Although developers work on AI systems more effectively due to the availability of Cloud Computing and parallel processing systems, they come at a price. Not everyone can afford that with an increase in the inflow of unprecedented amounts of data and rapidly increasing complex algorithms.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-9662e299-7fff-9446-ccb8-bd1d26dd422f">Conclusion</b></h2>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Businesses will have to familiarize themselves with AI, which will help them understand how AI works. There is no denying that implementing AI in businesses can have several challenges, and you will start noticing these challenges when creating an AI strategy for your business. However, adopting a step-by-step and strategic approach will simplify the process of AI implementation to a certain level.</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">If you&rsquo;re interested in updating more about technical knowledge, please stay tuned for the new Rikkeisoft blog!&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/572/4-challenges-of-ai-that-vietnam-it-companies-have-to-face/">4 challenges of AI that Vietnam IT Companies have to face</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/572/4-challenges-of-ai-that-vietnam-it-companies-have-to-face/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>One year look back: How Covid-19 affected the development of AI</title>
		<link>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/490/one-year-look-back-how-covid-19-affected-the-development-of-ai/</link>
					<comments>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/490/one-year-look-back-how-covid-19-affected-the-development-of-ai/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chitv@rikkeisoft.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 08:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Newsroom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rikkeisoft.com/2021/09/16/one-year-look-back-how-covid-19-affected-the-development-of-ai/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It is undeniable that COVID-19 has caused chaos and continued uncertainty for the global economy for the past two years. But surprisingly, despite the pandemic’s hit on the economy, the AI industry has shown positive signs of hectic growth from multiple perspectives. Overall in 2020, AI hiring, investment, and adoption significantly increased across the board, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/490/one-year-look-back-how-covid-19-affected-the-development-of-ai/">One year look back: How Covid-19 affected the development of AI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><meta charset="utf-8"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;"><em><strong>It is undeniable that COVID-19 has caused chaos and continued uncertainty for the global economy for the past two years. But surprisingly, despite the pandemic’s hit on the economy, the AI industry has shown positive signs of hectic growth from multiple perspectives. Overall in 2020, AI hiring, investment, and adoption significantly increased across the board, creating long-term trends that are here to stay even after the pandemic.</strong></em></p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="534" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/210917%20AI%20LOOK%20BACK_Mesa%20de%20trabajo%201%20copy.png" width="1600"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">According to The AI Index Report &#8211; an annual study of AI impact and progress established by Stanford HAI &#8211; the total global investment in AI, including private investment, public offerings, M&amp;A, and minority stakes, increased by 40% in 2020 relative to 2019 for a total of USD 67.9 billion.&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">In terms of private investment in AI startups, the global trend is that more money is being put into fewer companies. The report showed that there was a 9.3% increase in the amount of private AI investment (equivalent to more than 40B USD) into startups in 2020, while in 2019 the rate was 5.7%. However, the number of newly funded AI companies in the world continued a sharp decrease from its 2017 peak. The U.S remains the front runner for private investments (23.6B USD), while China stands in 2nd place with 9.9B USD, followed by the UK with 1.9B USD.</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="534" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/210917%20AI%20LOOK%20BACK_Mesa%20de%20trabajo%201%20copy%202.png" width="1600"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">AI Hirings data from LinkedIn shows that the number of AI hirings grow rapidly in the year 2020. The hiring rate has been surging across countries, in which Brazil, India, Canada, Singapore, and South Africa are the countries with the highest growth rate in AI hirings. It was also interesting to spot that hiring in the U.S. grew more slowly than in other countries, like Canada, Brazil, and South Africa. Indeed, the U.S. saw a decline in total AI job postings between 2019 and 2020 — from about 325,000 jobs to about 300,000 jobs. Some experts explain this event happens because the U.S is in fact further along the mass hiring stage of AI engineers, they are now a lot more mature and therefore more stable in terms of hiring numbers.</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Hiring demand going forward also suggests that AI’s application will soon become a “general-purpose” technology, like electricity, since AI can cut across almost all industries and the application of AI is indeed a wide-open door according to experts.</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="534" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/210917%20AI%20LOOK%20BACK_Mesa%20de%20trabajo%201%20copy%203.png" width="1600"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">The pandemic has paved the way for AI to enter businesses and proved its proficiency quicker than ever. In the new study, Thriving in an AI world, conducted by KPMG, a large number of business owners and government leaders stated that AI has now played a moderately to fully functional role within their organizations. The rate of AI adoption sky-rocketed during the Covid-19 pandemic, among which Industrial Manufacturing leads the poll at 93%, following Financial Services, Tech, and Retail at 84%, 83%, and 81% respectively. All three sectors including Financial Services, Tech, and Retail witnessed a great upward trend from the previous year of at least a 20% increase point, which clearly shows the businesses’ urge to apply AI in order to support and avoid discontinue of their operation.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Based on another report by McKinsey &amp; Company &#8211; “The State of AI in 2020”, Machine learning, robotic process automation (RPA), and computer vision appear to be the most popular AI technologies to be adopted across domains. Industries are likely to adopt AI capabilities that best serve their core functions. While Natural language processing (NLP) including text understanding, speech understanding, and text generation is frequently adopted by industries with high volumes of customer or operational data in text forms such as financial services, healthcare, and telecom; physical robotics, as well as autonomous vehicles, are most frequently adopted by industries where manufacturing and distribution play a larger role—such as automotive and assembly, and consumer goods and retail.</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="533" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/210917%20AI%20LOOK%20BACK_Mesa%20de%20trabajo%201%20copy%204.png" width="1600"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">Business leaders from both small and large companies say that AI helped their business, particularly during the Covid outbreak. While healthcare business leaders believe in the ability of AI to monitor the spread of COVID-19 cases, and help tremendously with vaccine development and distribution; in other sectors such as financial services, leaders are also confident that AI will be the game changer factor to help their company identify fraud, or in the public sector where decision-makers are certain in AI’s ability to improve bureaucratic efficiency.&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">The initial index also indicates that mentions of AI in corporate earnings calls have increased substantially and in 2020, the number of mentions of AI in earning calls was two times higher than mentions of big data, cloud, and machine learning combined. This has partly spoken volumes about the rising awareness of business leaders about the role of AI in their operation, as well as the contribution of AI adoption to increasing revenue and cutting costs of businesses.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: justify;">It is obvious that AI has been given a little push by the pandemic to accelerate, but some also worry that it may be moving too fast. Concerns focus mainly on the regulations needed to be set to ensure ethical AI technology and adoption, while some others think that companies will have to step up their game in changing broad contextual, including business process, leaders mindset, etc, in order to get the most of the technology.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/490/one-year-look-back-how-covid-19-affected-the-development-of-ai/">One year look back: How Covid-19 affected the development of AI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/490/one-year-look-back-how-covid-19-affected-the-development-of-ai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Creating useful products for people&#8217;s lives</title>
		<link>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/482/creating-useful-products-for-peoples-lives/</link>
					<comments>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/482/creating-useful-products-for-peoples-lives/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chitv@rikkeisoft.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 10:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Newsroom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rikkeisoft.com/2021/06/22/creating-useful-products-for-peoples-lives/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mr. Bui Quang Huy, CEO of Rikkei Japan, has been featured on The Human Story. We&#39;ve got a great summary for you below. &#160; Introduction&#160; &#160; Bui Quang Huy was born and raised in Vietnam. In 2009, while studying at the Hanoi University of Science and Technology, he received a scholarship at Ritsumeikan University and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/482/creating-useful-products-for-peoples-lives/">Creating useful products for people&#8217;s lives</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr"><meta charset="utf-8" /><b id="docs-internal-guid-4afc2d95-7fff-73a0-e6f5-f8f405ddc80a">Mr. Bui Quang Huy, CEO of Rikkei Japan, has been featured on The Human Story. We&#39;ve got a great summary for you below.</b></p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="812" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/%E1%BA%A2nh%20anh%20Huy%20JP.jpeg" width="800" /></p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><meta charset="utf-8" /></p>
<h3 dir="ltr"><b id="docs-internal-guid-99ae066e-7fff-e205-1dc4-a34506deec7b">Introduction&nbsp;</b></h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bui Quang Huy was born and raised in Vietnam. In 2009, while studying at the Hanoi University of Science and Technology, he received a scholarship at Ritsumeikan University and became one of the first students of the information technology human resource development program by JICA (Japan International Cooperation Agency).</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">After returning to Vietnam, Mr. Huy and his friends who studied at Ritsumeikan University and Keio University established Rikkeisoft Co., Ltd in 2012 &ndash; a software development company.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ricky Co., Ltd., a Japan subsidiary of Rikkeisoft, was established in 2016, and Mr. Huy was appointed as CEO in 2019.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ricky Co., Ltd.&#39;s primary business is software development, receiving projects from clients in Japan and the United States. Since 2019, the company has also been focusing on developing its own products/services, especially in the field of artificial intelligence (AI) and robotics.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr"><b id="docs-internal-guid-99ae066e-7fff-e205-1dc4-a34506deec7b">The Interview</b></h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><span style="font-size:20px;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-99ae066e-7fff-e205-1dc4-a34506deec7b">How did you get your current job?</b></span></p>
<p dir="ltr">After finishing two years studying in Japan, I returned to Vietnam and founded Rikkeisoft with five classmates. The origin of the company&rsquo;s name &quot;Rikkei&quot; is inspired by the names of Ritsumeikan University and Keio University, where the Rikkeisoft founders studied in Japan.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">During the first years of working at Rikkeisoft, I held the position of COO in Vietnam. In 2016, we established a legal entity in Japan, and I was in charge of the business here.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Rikkeisoft has grown rapidly and now has more than 1,200 employees, so we can research and develop a variety of different technology platforms and systems.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The language barrier factor is inevitable in overseas business development, but this is not a big problem for us. Many of our engineers can speak Japanese. Moreover, many engineers at Rikkeisoft have studied or lived in Japan, and they are familiar with the culture and working process. Therefore, our strength is the ability to communicate fluently in Japanese.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><span style="font-size:20px;"><b id="docs-internal-guid-99ae066e-7fff-e205-1dc4-a34506deec7b">Commitment to work</b></span></p>
<p dir="ltr">We started our business with the desire to prove to friends around the world the Vietnamese people&rsquo;s ability to create great things.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the future, we will cross the boundary between Vietnam and Japan towards the goal of exchanging personnel and building a global ecosystem. And I will also try to hone my skills to keep up with the times.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition, the image recognition application released by Rikkei.AI &ndash; a subsidiary of Rikkeisoft &ndash; can distinguish Vietnamese banknotes and support the lives of people with disabilities. The application is non-profit, and this is how we contribute to the community.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Rikkei.AI helps build and develop solutions, applying high technology such as eKYC, chatbots, speech-to-text, social media listening, and more.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the future, Rikkeisoft aims to reach the milestone of 10,000 employees, with Rikkei Co., Ltd. aiming to reach 1,000 people by 2025.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><span style="font-size:20px;"><strong>Message to young people</strong></span></p>
<p dir="ltr">If you find a dream, I think it will come true.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It doesn&rsquo;t take magic to make dreams come true. Do your best.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, no matter how hard you try and how good you are, it is not enough.</p>
<p dir="ltr">We need support from others and our colleagues. Always take care of your friends.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><b id="docs-internal-guid-99ae066e-7fff-e205-1dc4-a34506deec7b">FB: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/rikkeijapan/">https://www.facebook.com/rikkeijapan/</a></b></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/482/creating-useful-products-for-peoples-lives/">Creating useful products for people&#8217;s lives</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/482/creating-useful-products-for-peoples-lives/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rikkeisoft joined forces with PolkaFoundry, Sota Tek, and Ekoios to create a Blockchain R&#038;D network in the PolkaFoundry ecosystem.</title>
		<link>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/478/rikkeisoft-joined-forces-with-polkafoundry-sota-tek-and-ekoios-to-create-a-blockchain-rd-network-in-the-polkafoundry-ecosystem/</link>
					<comments>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/478/rikkeisoft-joined-forces-with-polkafoundry-sota-tek-and-ekoios-to-create-a-blockchain-rd-network-in-the-polkafoundry-ecosystem/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chitv@rikkeisoft.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 03:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Newsroom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rikkeisoft.com/2021/04/23/rikkeisoft-joined-forces-with-polkafoundry-sota-tek-and-ekoios-to-create-a-blockchain-rd-network-in-the-polkafoundry-ecosystem/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>April 16, 2021&#160;&#8211; In the drive to advance research and development for the Blockchain industry, four companies, composed of Rikkeisoft, PolkaFoundry, Sota Tek, and Ekoios, signed a Memorandum of Understanding, agreeing to support each other in a regional alliance. The PolkaDot Blockchain Development Association, or PBDA, will invest in specialized developer resources for decentralized apps [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/478/rikkeisoft-joined-forces-with-polkafoundry-sota-tek-and-ekoios-to-create-a-blockchain-rd-network-in-the-polkafoundry-ecosystem/">Rikkeisoft joined forces with PolkaFoundry, Sota Tek, and Ekoios to create a Blockchain R&#038;D network in the PolkaFoundry ecosystem.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><meta name="uuid" content="uuidiFehAiKCnYbm"><meta charset="utf-8"><strong>April 16, 2021</strong>&nbsp;&#8211; In the drive to advance research and development for the Blockchain industry, four companies, composed of Rikkeisoft, PolkaFoundry, Sota Tek, and Ekoios, signed a Memorandum of Understanding, agreeing to support each other in a regional alliance. The PolkaDot Blockchain Development Association, or PBDA, will invest in specialized developer resources for decentralized apps inside the PolkaFoundry network.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><em>&#8220;As a one-stop production hub for DeFi &amp; NFT applications on Polkadot, we established PBDA with the mission of not only contributes to the growth of the Polkadot ecosystem but also wishes to support all other blockchain projects that wish to the involved in the Polkadot Network in the journey from building strategic planning, product development to implement in real life. PBDA will become a reliable place for first-rate Polkadot developers to assist new Polkadot projects to solve any obstacles in developing decentralized applications on the Polkadot ecosystem without any fuss.&#8221; &#8211;&nbsp;</em>Truong Hong Thi, PolkaFoundry Founder/CEO of PolkaFoundry and PBDA Chairman</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="940" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/region1st%20alliance1.png" width="1600"></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>By pooling together resources, the alliance members will collaborate on finding, training, and building teams of experienced blockchain developers. These teams will maintain a development hub for projects in the PolkaDot ecosystem, especially for the PolkaFoundry platform.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&#8220;<em>Blockchain is a highly secure and applied technology. Before joining PBDA, SotaTek successfully implemented many projects for domestic and foreign customers, especially the cooperation with the Vietnamese government at the end of 2020. We hope that PBDA will be the launchpad for blockchain projects to thrive in the nearest future.” &#8211;</em>&nbsp;Luu Chung Tuyen, Sota Tek CEO</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="1200" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/region1st%20alliance2.png" width="1200"></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>A group of at least fifty will be ready during Quarter 2 of 2021, trained by industry professionals from each of the four allied companies.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>“A<em>s a pioneer company in the field of Blockchain, Ekoios has been developing a lot of blockchain products for customers.</em>&nbsp;B<em>y joining the PBDA, we will work with other members of the association to dig deeper and further to make blockchain technology even more developed while simultaneously bringing Vietnam into a world-class blockchain development center.</em>&#8221; &#8211; Mr. Do Dinh Dong, Ekoios CEO</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="1200" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/region1st%20alliance4.png" width="1200"></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The alliance of 2,000+ experienced industry professionals has tlihe capability to develop a center able to properly incubate a development hub, thanks to their years of experience working on projects from around the world. It will serve to connect the Polkadot ecosystem to the Southeast Asian blockchain network and improve the sustainability of the PolkaFoundry platform.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&#8220;This association is a combination of pioneering enterprises in research and development of Blockchain technology. In particular, we have built many successful blockchain projects and achieved attention from the international communities. Therefore, Rikkeisoft is very confident with this cooperation. The alliance will help us develop specialized human resources, making Vietnam the blockchain development center of the world, affirming Vietnamese technology capacity in the international arena.&#8221; &#8211; Phan The Dung, Rikkeisoft CEO</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="1200" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/region1st%20alliance3.png" width="1200"></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>We look forward to seeing the great things this alliance will do in accelerating blockchain application in Vietnam and in Raising Vietnamese Value.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/478/rikkeisoft-joined-forces-with-polkafoundry-sota-tek-and-ekoios-to-create-a-blockchain-rd-network-in-the-polkafoundry-ecosystem/">Rikkeisoft joined forces with PolkaFoundry, Sota Tek, and Ekoios to create a Blockchain R&#038;D network in the PolkaFoundry ecosystem.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/478/rikkeisoft-joined-forces-with-polkafoundry-sota-tek-and-ekoios-to-create-a-blockchain-rd-network-in-the-polkafoundry-ecosystem/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rikkeisoft: Building a Top-Class Dream Team in 2021</title>
		<link>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/561/rikkeisoft-building-a-top-class-dream-team-in-2021-2/</link>
					<comments>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/561/rikkeisoft-building-a-top-class-dream-team-in-2021-2/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chitv@rikkeisoft.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 11:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Newsroom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rikkeisoft.com/2021/03/12/rikkeisoft-building-a-top-class-dream-team-in-2021-2/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new recruitment strategy for 2021 &#160; Human resources is a hotly debated subject within Vietnamese business, particularly among Vietnamese IT professionals.&#160; &#160; According to forecasts, Vietnam will lack 900,000 IT professionals for the years 2020 and 2021. Additionally, the Vietnamese Ministry of Information and Communications states that although 50,000 developers graduate in Vietnam annually, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/561/rikkeisoft-building-a-top-class-dream-team-in-2021-2/">Rikkeisoft: Building a Top-Class Dream Team in 2021</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>A new recruitment strategy for 2021</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><meta charset="utf-8" /></p>
<p dir="ltr"><meta name="uuid" content="uuidWIhIkUftTEnQ" /><meta charset="utf-8" /></p>
<p>Human resources is a hotly debated subject within Vietnamese business, particularly among Vietnamese IT professionals.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to forecasts, Vietnam will lack 900,000 IT professionals for the years 2020 and 2021. Additionally, the Vietnamese Ministry of Information and Communications states that although 50,000 developers graduate in Vietnam annually, 72% lack practical skills, 42% lack team skills, and 80% need additional training. These highlight the strict requirements facing the Vietnamese IT industry. Therefore, if they are to find work, students need specialized knowledge, soft skills, and practical application to meet these challenges. Yet because of this, an opportunity to enhance the educational value of these institutions is presented.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Recognizing these facts, Rikkeisoft, having overcome the year 2020, decided to mark 2021 with another step forward. Keeping in mind the goal of increasing the total number of employees to 10,000, we endeavored to build the future developers of Vietnam by directly supporting their education.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="1036" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/image_2021_03_11T03_22_24_191Z.png" width="1600" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Building a Dream Team of Top-Class Developers</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="1067" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/aptech2.jpg" width="1600" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><em>March 10, 2021, Hanoi </em>&#8211; Rikkeisoft signed a long-term partnership agreement with Aptech Polytechnic University. Over 70 guests, Aptech students, and organization directors attended the ceremony.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Aptech Polytechnic, with its innovative inverse training model of &#39;Do First-Learn Later&#39;, has for many years trained and supplied human resources for the IT industry. Their hands-on model ensures students can find work immediately after graduation within their network of 200+ strategic partners.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Rikkeisoft will participate in this network by supporting a new curriculum called &quot;<strong>Training IT Leaders 4.0</strong>&quot;. We will do this by letting students learn in an actual working environment, where they will get the opportunity to meet with real industry professionals. The conditions afforded by this will then lend students practical knowledge, experience, and understanding of the software development industry. Students will need to complete 1200 hours of practice and 900 hours of lectures to finish the program.&nbsp;Rikkeisoft will support this by bringing the best equipment and staff available for students to get an insider&#39;s look at the industry. They will get to speak with experienced engineers, learn what to expect when going into a project, and, as proof of their qualifications upon completing the course, the ability to personally meet industry employers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Mr. Nguyen Viet Lam, Rikkeisoft&#39;s representative at the ceremony, had this to say: &quot;For the Vietnamese IT industry, there is a large number of people but a lack of highly qualified personnel. This leads to a shortage of quality human resources. Rikkeisoft hopes that this cooperation will bring benefit to both parties in the common goal of giving young talents a bright path to development and becoming Vietnamese IT stars.&quot;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="1200" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/157748242_3883663325052987_342993725108547465_o.jpg" width="800" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Within this framework, Rikkeisoft-brand courses and exchanges will supplement the student&#39;s education, which will go a long way toward creating recruitment opportunities among Vietnam&#39;s future IT developers.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Mr. Nguyen Duy Quang, Aptech Polytechnic&#39;s Director, wished Rikkeisoft and other partners the best in creating a high-quality training program for their students.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="1200" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/DSC_6200.jpg" width="806" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>With luck, this long-term partnership will profit both Rikkeisoft and Aptech Polytechnic, thanks to the strides made together in training, developing, and supplying high-quality IT human resources.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/561/rikkeisoft-building-a-top-class-dream-team-in-2021-2/">Rikkeisoft: Building a Top-Class Dream Team in 2021</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/561/rikkeisoft-building-a-top-class-dream-team-in-2021-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rikkeisoft International Women&#8217;s Day 2021</title>
		<link>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/474/rikkeisoft-international-womens-day-2021/</link>
					<comments>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/474/rikkeisoft-international-womens-day-2021/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chitv@rikkeisoft.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Newsroom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rikkeisoft.com/2021/03/09/rikkeisoft-international-womens-day-2021/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#160; &#160; March 8 is International Women&#39;s Day. &#160; Every year in Vietnam, it is a tradition for men to give women gifts and hold parties in their honor. Rikkeisoft is no different. &#160; This year, the men of Rikkeisoft pretended to be couriers.&#160; &#160; Since the Vietnamese internet economy is booming, the girls at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/474/rikkeisoft-international-womens-day-2021/">Rikkeisoft International Women&#8217;s Day 2021</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><meta charset="utf-8" /></p>
<p dir="ltr"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="467" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/8_3333_Mesa%20de%20trabajo%201(1).jpg" width="701" /></p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><b id="docs-internal-guid-07379fbc-7fff-7427-7aa1-27beb79f756e">M</b><strong>arch 8 is International Women&#39;s Day.</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Every year in Vietnam, it is a tradition for men to give women gifts and hold parties in their honor.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
Rikkeisoft is no different.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This year, the men of Rikkeisoft pretended to be couriers.&nbsp;</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="697" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/womensdaya2.jpg" width="697" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Since the Vietnamese internet economy is booming, the girls at our company receive packages and talk with couriers daily. So, using that to their advantage, our boys hoped to surprise the girls, add an element of excitement, and make the day more memorable than years past.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="700" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/womensdaya7.jpg" width="700" /></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="700" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/womensdaya4.jpg" width="700" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>On the day of, the women of Rikkei received a phone call, telling them they&#39;ve received an anonymous package. Wondering who their &quot;Secret Admirer&quot; was and what the contents were, our girls were very excited, knowing that it was Woman&#39;s Day. Whether at the office, on-site with a customer, or on maternity leave, the Rikkeisoft courier team reached every doorstep and made everyone&#39;s Women&#39;s Day one to remember.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="924" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/womensdaya3.jpg" width="692" /></p>
<p dir="ltr"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="900" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/womensdaya5.png" width="675" /></p>
<p dir="ltr"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="900" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/womensdaya6.png" width="675" /></p>
<p dir="ltr"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="900" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/womensdaya1.jpg" width="675" /></p>
<p dir="ltr">Happy International Women&#39;s Day.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
From Rikkeisoft.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/474/rikkeisoft-international-womens-day-2021/">Rikkeisoft International Women&#8217;s Day 2021</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/474/rikkeisoft-international-womens-day-2021/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A look back at the year 2020</title>
		<link>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/472/a-look-back-at-the-year-2020-2/</link>
					<comments>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/472/a-look-back-at-the-year-2020-2/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chitv@rikkeisoft.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 10:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Newsroom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rikkeisoft.com/2020/12/31/a-look-back-at-the-year-2020-2/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We can surely speak for everyone when we say that 2020 was a very difficult year. Though it started out with promise, the Covid-19 pandemic forced us all to change our plans, leaving us with a year like no other. However, despite all the hardship, we were able to overcome and make a lot of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/472/a-look-back-at-the-year-2020-2/">A look back at the year 2020</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We can surely speak for everyone when we say that 2020 was a very difficult year. Though it started out with promise, the Covid-19 pandemic forced us all to change our plans, leaving us with a year like no other. However, despite all the hardship, we were able to overcome and make a lot of happy memories that we&rsquo;ll be able to take with us into the new year. As such, we&rsquo;d like to take this final moment to thank our loyal customers and employees for their support and reflect on some of the milestones we achieved this year.</p>
<p><meta charset="utf-8" /></p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><span style="font-size:16px;"><strong>1. We opened an office in Osaka</strong></span></p>
<p dir="ltr">We started the year on a positive note, moving into the vibrant downtown area of Chaya-machi. Opening a second Japanese office was no small feat, so we commemorated getting started in our fifth city by having a party at the InterContinental Osaka hotel. Led by Managing Director, Nakamura Keisuke, our Osaka office has already shown great signs of success and is expected to continue doing so as we move into the next year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="1104" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/Osara%20branch(1).jpg" width="1600" /></p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><span style="font-size:16px;"><strong>2. Rikkeisoft anti-pandemic measures were a success!</strong></span><meta charset="utf-8" /></p>
<p dir="ltr">We were all forced into lockdown by the Covid-19, but that didn&rsquo;t stop us from continuing to deliver quality products for all of our customers. Even while we were working from home, and especially during the second wave, we made extra sure to keep delivering on our promises, all while making sure we complied with social distancing. As a result, we were able to keep business running as usual.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="1200" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/1596683150573.jpg" width="900" /></p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><span style="font-size:16px;"><strong>3. Rikkeisoft set a new mission, vision, and core values!</strong></span></p>
<p dir="ltr"><meta charset="utf-8" /></p>
<p dir="ltr">We had to change ourselves, to not only deliver quality products to our partners, but also to do our part to build a better society. We decided to change ourselves to better take on new global markets! Aspiration, Improvement, Dedication, Innovation, Openness&hellip; These values will no doubt serve us well as we Raise Vietnamese Value and aim for the top spot in the world of Vietnamese technology.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="901" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/Core%20value.jpg" width="901" /></p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><span style="font-size:16px;"><strong>4.&nbsp;We raised 3 million USD in capital and transitioned from a privately-held limited company into a joint stock-held corporation</strong></span><meta charset="utf-8" /></p>
<p dir="ltr">When we started in 2012, we were just six friends working together in one cramped apartment. Now that we&#39;d grown to a company of 1,200+, we needed to restructure ourselves to better function in the rapidly changing world of enterprises. In Vietnam, only a few local companies have the size necessary to call themselves a corporation and we are proud to be included on this exclusive list.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="721" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/corporation.jpg" width="1280" /></p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><span style="font-size:16px;"><strong>5.&nbsp;We donated computers and rebuilt schools for minority communities!</strong></span><meta charset="utf-8" /></p>
<p dir="ltr">Our company ventured into the border regions to do our part to Raise Vietnamese Value. For example, in the storm-affected province of Quang Nam, we raised 400 million VND to help the local schools and towns get back on their feet. Not hoping to leave the people of Dien Bien out, we went to their province to donate computers, bringing them firmly into the 21st century. This isn&rsquo;t to forget, finally, our trip to Ha Giang where we inaugurated a new school, which will help keep the children warm as they study in the cold winter months.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="900" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/charity%203.JPG" width="1600" /></p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><span style="font-size:16px;"><strong>6.&nbsp;We signed a strategic partnership with Oraichain!</strong></span></p>
<p dir="ltr">We secured the chance of a lifetime, when we signed up with the world&rsquo;s first AI-powered Data Oracle Platform! Supporting them with our experts, 2021 is expected to be a year in which our two companies will take the blockchain world by storm! Our Chairman and CEO are both themselves getting involved, signing on as advisors to help them on their rise to stardom!</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="1113" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/DSC_2790.JPG" width="1600" /></p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><span style="font-size:16px;"><strong>7.&nbsp;Rikkeisoft won at the 2020 Top 10 Vietnam ICT Companies!</strong></span></p>
<p dir="ltr"><meta charset="utf-8" /></p>
<p dir="ltr">We were proud to be awarded VINASA&rsquo;s prestigious awards for our work in the fields of Outsourcing and AI/IoT. 2020 was the first year that the awards were separated into different categories, so that we were recognized as leaders in these fields shows just how hard we&rsquo;ve been working this year! We look forward to distinguishing ourselves again in next year&rsquo;s edition!</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img loading="lazy" alt="" height="1200" src="https://rikkeisoft.com/wp-content/themes/main/assets/ckfinder/images/Top10ICT.jpg" width="1585" /></p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><meta charset="utf-8" /></p>
<p dir="ltr">All in all, 2020 proved to be a year unlike any other. For all its downs, it also had its ups, and there were lessons to be learned from each new memory we made. Our deepest gratitude for the last eight years of support and we hope to see you again in the years to come!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/472/a-look-back-at-the-year-2020-2/">A look back at the year 2020</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://rikkeisoft.com">Rikkeisoft - Your trusted IT provider</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://rikkeisoft.com/newsroom/472/a-look-back-at-the-year-2020-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
